[
    {
        "front": "おもいます ❘",
        "back": "To think",
        "chapter": 21
    },
    {
        "front": "いいます ❘",
        "back": "To say",
        "chapter": 21
    },
    {
        "front": "たります ❘",
        "back": "To be enough, be sufficient",
        "chapter": 21
    },
    {
        "front": "かちます ❘",
        "back": "To win",
        "chapter": 21
    },
    {
        "front": "まけます ❘❘",
        "back": "To lose, to be beaten",
        "chapter": 21
    },
    {
        "front": "あります ❘\n[おまつりが～]",
        "back": "[a festival] be held, take place",
        "chapter": 21
    },
    {
        "front": "やくに たちます ❘",
        "back": "be useful",
        "chapter": 21
    },
    {
        "front": "むだ [な]",
        "back": "wasteful",
        "chapter": 21
    },
    {
        "front": "ふべん [な]",
        "back": "inconvenient",
        "chapter": 21
    },
    {
        "front": "おなじ",
        "back": "the same",
        "chapter": 21
    },
    {
        "front": "すごい",
        "back": "Amazing, great (expresses astonishment or admiration)",
        "chapter": 21
    },
    {
        "front": "しゅしょう",
        "back": "Prime minister",
        "chapter": 21
    },
    {
        "front": "だいとうりょう",
        "back": "President",
        "chapter": 21
    },
    {
        "front": "せいじ",
        "back": "Politics",
        "chapter": 21
    },
    {
        "front": "ニュース",
        "back": "News",
        "chapter": 21
    },
    {
        "front": "スピーチ",
        "back": "Speech (～します: make a speech)",
        "chapter": 21
    },
    {
        "front": "しあい",
        "back": "Game, match",
        "chapter": 21
    },
    {
        "front": "アルバイト",
        "back": "Part time job （～します: work part time)",
        "chapter": 21
    },
    {
        "front": "いけん",
        "back": "opinion",
        "chapter": 21
    },
    {
        "front": "[お] はなし",
        "back": "talk, speech, story (～します: talk, tell a story)",
        "chapter": 21
    },
    {
        "front": "ユーモア",
        "back": "humor",
        "chapter": 21
    },
    {
        "front": "むだ",
        "back": "waste",
        "chapter": 21
    },
    {
        "front": "デザイン",
        "back": "design",
        "chapter": 21
    },
    {
        "front": "こうつう",
        "back": "transportation, traffic",
        "chapter": 21
    },
    {
        "front": "ラッシュ",
        "back": "rush hour",
        "chapter": 21
    },
    {
        "front": "さいきん",
        "back": "recently, these days",
        "chapter": 21
    },
    {
        "front": "たぶん",
        "back": "probably, perhaps, maybe",
        "chapter": 21
    },
    {
        "front": "きっと",
        "back": "surely",
        "chapter": 21
    },
    {
        "front": "ほんとうに",
        "back": "really",
        "chapter": 21
    },
    {
        "front": "そんなに",
        "back": "not so much (used with negatives)",
        "chapter": 21
    },
    {
        "front": "～に  ついて",
        "back": "about~, related to~",
        "chapter": 21
    },
    {
        "front": "しかたが  ありません",
        "back": "There is no other choice / We have no way out",
        "chapter": 21
    },
    {
        "front": "しばらくですね",
        "back": "it's been a long time since we met",
        "chapter": 21
    },
    {
        "front": "～でも  のみませんか",
        "back": "How about drinking ~ or something?",
        "chapter": 21
    },
    {
        "front": "みないと...",
        "back": "I've got to watch it",
        "chapter": 21
    },
    {
        "front": "もちろん",
        "back": "of course",
        "chapter": 21
    }
]